http://www.ozstick.com.au/information/privacy-policy/

PO Box 7068, Croydon South, VIC 3136 |
Ph. 0401 845 726 | info@ozstick.com.au
$0.000 items
Checkout
This Privacy Policy tells you how we collect information when you visit this site or deal with us and what we do with your personal information.
We understand the importance you attach to your personal information. As such, we shall ensure that we comply with our obligations under the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth).
If you submit information to OzStick by registering as a member, purchasing one of our products or by sending us an email, we collect that information and use it for the purposes of providing you with information or advice about our goods and/or services and for processing an order by you for our goods and/or services.
Specifically, we require your name, street address, email address, phone and fax number and method of payment details in order to complete an order for our goods and/or services.
We shall only disclose your personal information to third parties where the disclosure is necessary and directly related to the purposes set out above – such as our financial institution to process your order. We shall not give our customer lists to third parties for promotions independent of OzStick. Please note that our payment processing is done via third party sites (e.g. PayPal) and any confirmation we receive from them of your payment will NEVER include your Credit/Debit Card details.
Under the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth) you have a right to request access to your personal information held by us. You may do this by sending us an email to info@ozstick.com.au or by writing to us at:
Privacy OfficerOzStick Pty LtdP.O. Box 7068Croydon South VIC 3136
You do not have to provide us with the information requested, however, we will be unable to process your order should you be unwilling to do so.
If you have any questions/comments about privacy, you should contact us.
